Eddie Woods papers, circa 1957-2009 M1386
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - Levy, William: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Levy, William: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Levy, William: Correspondence, Poems, and Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Levy, William: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Levy, William: Correspondence (Incoming/Outgoing) and Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Levy, William: Natural Jewboy (Typesetter's copy and softcover book) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Levy, William: Natural Jewboy (Hardcover Book) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Levy, Ernesto and Edith Godik (aka E and E): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Levy, Ernesto and Edith Godik (aka E and E): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Libertine: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Logan, Alistair: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Lorsch, Emanuel (Mike): Talking to the Invisible Worlds (Manuscript) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Lyssiotis, Peter: Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - MacAdams, Lewis: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - MacLise, Angus: Correspondence and Poems (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Malanga, Gerard: Poems and Ephemera (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Malanga, Gerard: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Malanga, Gerard: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Incoming/Outgoing), and Ephemera (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Malanga, Gerard: Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Malik, Muhammad Akram and Jack McDonald: Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Manders, A.J. M. (Swami Sri Ram): Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Marcinko, Bill-Dale: Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Marpa: Ephemera (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Mathisen, Thor: The Traveller (Manuscript) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Mayo, Michael: The Day After (Poem) (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - McClure, Michael: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - McCurry, Jim: Poems (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - McDonald, Jack: Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - McGeehan, Charles: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - McGeehan, Charles: Correspondence and Poems (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - McGeehan, Charles: Poems (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - McGeehan, Charles: Poems and Correspondence (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Messina, Maria: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Micheline, Jack: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Micheline, Jack: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Micheline, Jack: Artwork, Slides, and Ephemera (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Micheline, Jack: Artwork, Poems, and Correspondence (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Micheline, Jack: Notes of the Lost Cities 1955-1963 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Micheline, Jack: Poems of Fire and Light and notebook with poems, journals, notes, letters, and collages 1957-1982 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Henry: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Stephanie: Poems (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Minkoff, George Robert: Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera (Including Chapbook,Eddie Woods Timeline, and Correspondence) (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correpondence (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Personal Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Personal Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Moe, David: Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Mona (Mona Winslow): Correspondence and Poetry (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Monsen, Hans Christian: Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Moonbeam: Poems and Short Stories (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Morrel, Marc: Correspondence, Photographs, and Poems (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Morris, Richard: The International Association of Independent Publishers' Cosmep Catalogue (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Morris, Richard: Oscar: A Novel (Manuscript) (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Morris, Richard: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Mortimer, Peter: Correspondence and Poems (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Mouly, Francoise: Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Mudry, Elizabeth: Correspondence and Snow White and 7 Dwarves (Short Story) (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Mueller, Jack (John): Correspondence, Poems, and The Budada Manifesto (Manuscript) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Mueller, Marnie: Correspondence and The Soldiers Who Guard Us at Tule Lake (Short Story) (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Muirhead, Dennis: Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Mycue, Edward: Book and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Myers, Vali: Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Naber, Lucienne (aka Ma Prem Prakash): Correspondence, Poems, and Photograph (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Nations, Opal: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Navat, Larry: Correspondence and Poems (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Nim, Peter: Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Nixon, Rob and Robin Fennel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Nardmann, Anne: Correspondence and Photographs (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Norse, Harold: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Nyanaloka Maha Thera: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - O'Donnell, Peter: Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Odamtten, Vincent: My Rings and Other Knick-Knacks (Manuscript) (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Oisteanu, Andrei: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Oisteanu, Valery: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Olson, Kirby: Correspondence and Poems (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Oswald, Ernest Jay: Correspondence and Poems (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Owens, Tuppy: Correspondence and Biography Summary (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Ozon, Diana: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Pake and Julie: Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Petra: Correspondence and Photograph (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Peabody, Richard (Rick): Correspondence and Photograph (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Pearlman, Allen: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Pell, Derek: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Penzler, Otto: Correspondence and Article (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Peterson, Tom: Correspondence and Book Review (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Phillippi, Thomas: Born Under No Star (Manuscript) (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Phillips, Zalmer: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Piromalli, Aldo: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Plantenga, Bart: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Plantenga, Bart: Chapbooks, Correspondence, and Ephemera (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Plomp, Hans: Correspondence and Poems (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Plomp, Hans: Translation of Piero Heliczer Manuscripts (by Plomp) (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Plomp, Hans: Poems, Articles, and Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Plomp, Hans: Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Plomp, Hans: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Plomp, Hans: Poems and Ephemera (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Plymell, Charles: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Pociao (Sylvia Pogorzalek): Correspondence, Poems, and Photograph (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Polesky, Alice: Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Pollack, Rachel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Poniewaz, Jeff: Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Ponsot, Claude: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Posset, Benn: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Pruzan, Robert: Photographs and Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Rastafolk, The (Bobby and Mary): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Raworth, Tom: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Richkin, Robert: Correspondence and Poems (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Richman, Harry: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Riklin, Scott: Correspondence (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Rinciari, Ken: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Ro, Emanuel: Correspondence and Poems (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Robie, Bozzie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Roditi, Edouard: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Rodriguez, Manuel (known as Spain or Spain Rodriguez): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Rogalska, Gina: Correspondence and Poems (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Rose, Edward: Correspondence (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Rubington, Norman (aka Akbar del Piombo): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Russo, Albert: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Rutz, Charles: Correspondence (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Ryan, Dave Stuart: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Samten, Karma: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Sanchez, Ricardo: Correspondence, Poem, and Business Card (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Sanders, Chris: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Sanders, Chris: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Sanders, Chris: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Sands, Vermillion: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Sands, Vermillion: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Santu, Mariposa (Elliot Rubenstein): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Sauer, Ronald: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Schippers, Huib: Correspondence, Ephemera, and Wereldmuziek (Magazine) (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Schouten, Arthur: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Schwartz, Stephen: Poem (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Seager, Moe: Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Seeger, Pete: Ephemera (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Shiodasani, Mohan: Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Simon, Leslie: Correspondence and Poems (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Smidt, Alexander (Lex): Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Barbara: Poem and Short Story (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Snell, A.L.: Poems (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Snyder, Don: Correspondence, Photographs, and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Sofia, Constantino (Tino): Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Spratt, Jack: Poems (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Starvin' Marvin: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Stephenson, Gregory: Correspondence, Poems, and Pearl Literary Magazine (no. 5, 7, and 8) (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Stettner, Irving: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Stettner, Irving: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Stevens, Peter: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Stone, Bernard: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Stoute, Henrik: Correspondence and Poems (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Stoute, Rene: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Streit, Bernard: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Strete, Craig: Poem and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Sylvester, Bruce: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Szkarosi, Endre: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Tajiri (Shinkichi Tagiri): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Taylor, Michael (Magic Mike): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Tekhova, Zlata: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Thiele, Don Alfred: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Thomas, Lorenzo: Correspondence and Poems (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Thue, Christina: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Tillman, Lynne: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Tillson, Jake: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Timmerman, Kenneth: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Tofer, Merle: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Trantino, Tommy: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Tyson, Bill: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Ubink, Babette: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Ubink, Babette: Correspondence (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Ubink, Babette: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Uitgeverij 261 (Hennie Jetzes): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Valaoritis, Nanos: Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Valenza, Roberto: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - van Dam, Eva: Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - van Dam, Johannes: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - van de Louw, Hennie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Van Den Ven, Andreas (Toshen): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - van der Does, Henk (and wife Goca): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Van Der Veen, Anthony (Tony): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - van Schalk, Vera: Poems (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - van Vugt, Ewald: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Vega, Janine Pommy: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Veltmeyer, Frank: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Venn, Frederica: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Verhagen, Peter: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Vinkenoog, Simon: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Volgarino, Gino: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Walden, Tisa: Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Walden, Anne: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Weber, Harold J.: Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Weichel, Ken: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Weinstein, William: Correspondence and Essays (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Weiss, Steve: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Weissner, Carl: Correspondence and Poems (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Wetterhahn, Kristen: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Whetstyne, Rebecca: Correspondence and White Sheets Chapbook (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Whitman, George: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Wilcock, John: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Heathcote (and Richard Adams): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Malcolm: Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Williams, Tennesee: Correspondence from Eddie Woods (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Wilson, Kirke: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Wilson, Tom: Faster than Cool-Aid (Poem) (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Winans, A.D.: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Wolak, Bill: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Wondratschek, Wolf: Correspondence and an Interview (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Young, Sally: Correspondence and Art Postcards (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Z., Emmanuel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Zabel, Ed: Correspondence and Photographs (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Ziman, Larry: Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Zinovitch, Jordan: Correspondence and Poem (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Zinancevic, Nina: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Series 2: Ins and Outs
  This series contains correspondence, layout sheets, production ephemera, and miscellaneous artwork relating to both E & J Enterprises and Ins and Outs. It also contains Ins and Outs answering machine messages both handwritten and typed. The audio cassettes which contain the recordings of the answering machine messages are described in Series 9. Audiovisual Materials.
  - Ins and Outs: Correspondence, Ephemera, and Eddie Woods Timeline (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Ins and Outs: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Ins and Outs: Business Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - E & J Enterprises: Business Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Ins and Outs: Business Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Ins and Outs: Business Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Ins and Outs: Business Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Ins and Outs: Bookstore Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Ins and Outs: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Ins and Outs: Layout Sheets (Issue #4/5) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Ins and Outs: Miscellaneous Typesettings and Layouts (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Ins and Outs: Miscellaneous Typesettings and Layouts (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Ins and Outs: Miscellaneous Artwork 10 Identified Artists (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Ins and Outs: Melkweg Ad (Original Artwork, Acetate Transparency, and Positive Copy Proof) (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Ins and Outs: Miscellaneous Artwork and Photographs (Artist Unknown) (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Ins and Outs: Mark Leggo (Staff Artist, Issue #2) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Ins and Outs: Original Production Copy for the Harold Norse of Course Cassette Cover (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Ins and Outs: Corrections of Natural Jewboy Manuscript (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Ins and Outs: Production Copy of Issue #4/5 (1 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Ins and Outs: Production Copy of Issue #4/5 (2 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Ins and Outs: Postcard Catalogue Production Copy (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Ins and Outs: Handwritten Library Lists (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Ins and Outs: Original Design for Not Realeased Press Catalog (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Ins and Outs: Production Artwork #1 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Ins and Outs: Production Artwork #2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Ins and Outs: Production Artwork #3 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Ins and Outs: printers Film for Jack Micheline Cassette Cover (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Ins and Outs: Business Files (University and Library Related) (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Ins and Outs: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Ins and Outs: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera (Includes banking checks, distribution lists, subscription royalty records, etc.) (Box 76)
  - Old Mailing List File Cards and Inventory list from September 28, 1981 (Box 77)
  - Ins & Outs Rubber Stamps (Box 78)
  - Ins and Outs Miscellaneous Mailing Lists (on index cards) (Box 79)
  - Ins and Outs Press: Texts of Prescripted Answering Machine Messages (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Ins and Outs Press: Answering Machine Messages (Text) (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Ins and Outs Production Artwork (Map-folder 20)
  - Ins and Outs Layout Boards Issue #1 (Map-folder 22)
  - Ins and Outs Layout Boards Issue #2 (Map-folder 23)
  - Ins and Outs Oversize Production Ephemera (Flat-box 92, Folder 2)
  - Ins and Outs Handmade Wooden Sign (Flat-box 90, Item 1)
  - Ins and Outs Open/Closed Door Sign (Flat-box 90, Item 2)
- Series 3: Eddie Woods' Diaries
  This series contains originals and copies of Eddie Woods' travel diaries from 1974 - 1980. It also contains photocopies of incoming/outgoing correspondence between Eddie Woods and Jane Harvey which constitue part of Eddie Woods' travel journal. Eddie Woods' diary while staying in Devon with Jenny Brookes is described in Series 9. Jenny Brookes.
  - Eddie Woods' London Journal: November 29, 1976 - July 6, 1977 (Original and Photocopy) (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Eddie Woods' Travel Diary: January 1976 - December 1976 (Original and Photocopy) (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Eddie Woods' Travel Diary: January 1976 - December 1976 (Additional Photocopy) (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Eddie Woods' Travel Diary (June 1974 - July 1974, May 1975) (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Eddie Woods and Jane Harvey: Correspondence 1974-1988 (Photocopies) [Constitute Part of Eddie Wood's Travel Journals] (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Eddie Woods Diary: Early 1979 - May 1980 (Mostly Amsterdam, Original and Photocopy) (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Eddie Woods' Diary: March 1978 - March 1979 (Original and Partial Transcript) (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Eddie Woods' Diary and Notes: November 1977 - March 1978 (Original and Photocopy) (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Eddie Woods' Travel Notes: 1974 - 1976 (Original Only) (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Series 4: Little Magazines
  - 15 Minutes [St. Louis, Missouri]: Issue, 12, 1991 (Box 18)
  - 39 Blows [Johnny Dolphin]: 1985 (Box 18)
  - 925 [Australia]: No. 6 (Box 18)
  - Abracadabra [Luxembourg]: No. 2, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Abracadabra [Luxembourg]: November 1979 (Box 18)
  - Adam [United Kingdom]: Nos. 410-412, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson):Vol. 14, No.4–Vol. 15, No. 1, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 18, No. 3, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 18, No. 2, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 18, No. 4–Vol. 19, No. 1, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 19, Nos. 2–3, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 19, No. 4–Vol. 20, No. 1, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 20, Nos. 3–4, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 20, No. 2, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 21, No. 1, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 21, No. 2, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 21, No. 3, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 21, No. 4–Vol. 22, No. 1, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
  - Agenda [United Kingdom, W. Cookson, editor] (Includes correspondence with W. Cookson): Vol. 22, Nos. 3–4, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Akzente [Germany]: No. 4, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Alcheringa [Boston, Mass.]: Vol. 2, No. 2, 1976 (Box 18)
  - All the Poets [United Kingdom]: 1979 (Box 18)
  - Alpha versus Omega: 1990? (Box 18)
  - Alph Null [Washington, D.C.]: No. 1.5, 1983 (Box 18)
  - ALPS Monthly [San Francisco, Calif.]: Vol. 3, No. 4, Issue 25, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Das Alternative Adressbuch [Germany]: 1979 (Box 18)
  - Alternative Media [New York] (Includes EW photocopies of correspondence to/from Craig Silver, editor, 1980-1983]: Vol. 14, No. 1, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Alternative Media [New York] (Includes EW photocopies of correspondence to/from Craig Silver, editor, 1980-1983]: Vol. 14, No. 2, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Alternative Press Syndicate [New York]: 1980 (Box 19)
  - Alternative Press Syndicate [New York]: 1982-1983 (Box 19)
  - Ambit [London]: No. 81, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Ambit [London]: No. 83, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Ambit [London]: No. 85, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Ambit [London]: No. 86, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Ambit [London]: No. 87, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Ambit [London]: No. 90, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Ambit [London]: No. 92, 1983 (Box 19)
  - American Book Review: Vol. 11, No. 6, 1990 (Box 19)
  - Amok Koma [Germany]: 1980 (Box 19)
  - Amsterdam, Amsterdam [Simon Vinkenoog]: 1978 (Box 19)
  - Amsterdams Ballon Gezelschap [Plomp]: No. 6, 1981? (Box 19)
  - Anarchism: Arguments For & Against [A. Meltzer]: 1981 (Box 19)
  - Anarchism: The Feminist Connection [Peggy Kornegger]: 1977 (Box 19)
  - Anarchism & Marxism [Daniel Guerin]: 1981 (Box 19)
  - Anarchist Review [United Kingdom, Cienfuegos Press, Stuart Christie, editor]: Vol. 1, No. 3, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Anarchist Review [United Kingdom, Cienfuegos Press, Stuart Christie, editor]: Vol. 1, No. 5 (Box 19)
  - Anarcho-feminism [Black Bear]: 1977 (Box 19)
  - Anarchy [JR White]: 1981? (Box 19)
  - Androgyne [San Francisco, Calif. Ken Weichel, editor]: No. 2, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Androgyne [San Francisco, Calif. Ken Weichel, editor]: No. 3, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Androgyne [San Francisco, Calif. Ken Weichel, editor]: No. 4, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Androgyne [San Francisco, Calif. Ken Weichel, editor]: No. 6, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Androgyne [San Francisco, Calif. Ken Weichel, editor]: No. 7, 1982 (Box 19)
  - The Angel / L'Angelo (with Lewis Macadams): 1980 (Box 19)
  - Anoixth [Greece]: No. 2, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Anoixth [Greece]: No. 3, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Antaeus: No. 38, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Antaeus: No. 39, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Anti-Statist Communist Manifesto [J. Lane]: 1978 (Box 20)